{"questions":[{"question":"Which of the following best describes \"head arrangement\" as the term is used in line 11?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"A published version of a gospel song produced for use by Black singers"},{"key":"B","answer":"A gospel song based on a slave spiritual"},{"key":"C","answer":"A musical score shared by a gospel singer and a  jazz musician"},{"key":"D","answer":"An informally written composition intended for  use by a gospel singer"},{"key":"E","answer":"An improvised performance inspired by the  singer's emotions"}],"right":["E"],"parent":0},{"question":"The author mentions \"folk fashion\" (line 4) most likely in order to","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"counter an assertion about the role of improvisation in music created by Black people"},{"key":"B","answer":"compare early gospel music with gospel music written later in the twentieth century"},{"key":"C","answer":"make a distinction between gospel music and slave spirituals"},{"key":"D","answer":"introduce a discussion about the dissemination of slave spirituals"},{"key":"E","answer":"describe a similarity between gospel music and slave spirituals"}],"right":["C"],"parent":0},{"question":"The passage suggests which of the following about Black gospel music and slave spirituals?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"Both became widely known in the early twentieth century."},{"key":"B","answer":"Both had an important improvisatory element."},{"key":"C","answer":"Both were frequently performed by jazz musicians."},{"key":"D","answer":"Both were published with only a vocal line and piano accompaniment."},{"key":"E","answer":"Both were disseminated chiefly by Black singing groups."}],"right":["B"],"parent":0},{"question":"Of the following sentences, which is most likely to have immediately preceded the passage?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"Few composers of gospel music drew on traditions such as the spiritual in creating their songs."},{"key":"B","answer":"Spirituals and Black gospel music were derived from the same musical tradition."},{"key":"C","answer":"The creation and singing of spirituals, practiced by Black Americans before the Civil War, continued after the war."},{"key":"D","answer":"Spirituals and gospel music can be clearly distinguished from one another."},{"key":"E","answer":"Improvisation was one of the primary characteristics of the gospel music created by Black musicians."}],"right":["B"],"parent":0},{"question":"The author of the passage is primarily concerned with","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"describing how the principles of classical chemistry were developed"},{"key":"B","answer":"initiating a debate about the kinds of chemical reactions required for the development of life"},{"key":"C","answer":"explaining how current research in chemistry may be related to broader biological concerns"},{"key":"D","answer":"reconciling opposing theories about chemical reactions"},{"key":"E","answer":"clarifying inherent ambiguities in the laws of classical chemistry"}],"right":["C"],"parent":1},{"question":"According tothe passage, classical chemical reactions and tunneling reactions are alike in which of the following ways?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"In both types of reactions, reacting molecules have to rise over the barrier between the two wells."},{"key":"B","answer":"In both types of reactions, a transition is made from the bottom of one potential well to the bottom of another."},{"key":"C","answer":"In neither type of reaction does the height of the barrier between the wells remain constant."},{"key":"D","answer":"In neither type of reaction does the rate of a chemical reaction depend on its activation energy."},{"key":"E","answer":"In both types of reactions, reacting molecules are able to go through the barrier between the two wells."}],"right":["B"],"parent":1},{"question":"According to the Arrhenius equation as discussed in the passage, which of the following statements about chemical reactions is true?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"Chemical reactions are less likely to occur at temperatures close to absolute zero."},{"key":"B","answer":"In some cases the rate of a chemical reaction is related to temperature and in other cases it is not."},{"key":"C","answer":"Chemical reactions frequently occur at a few degrees above absolute zero, but they are very unpredictable."},{"key":"D","answer":"The rate of a chemical reaction depends on many other factors besides temperature."},{"key":"E","answer":"Chemical reaction rate and temperature are not related."}],"right":["A"],"parent":1},{"question":"The author's attitude toward the theory of a cold prehistory of life can best be described as","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"neutral"},{"key":"B","answer":"skeptical"},{"key":"C","answer":"mildly positive"},{"key":"D","answer":"very supportive"},{"key":"E","answer":"pointedly critical"}],"right":["C"],"parent":1},{"question":"The author's hypothesis concerning be cold prehistory of life would be most weakened if which of the following were true?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"Cosmic rays are unlikely to trigger the formation of simple molecules."},{"key":"B","answer":"Tunneling occurs only in a narrow band of temperatures around zero degrees Kelvin."},{"key":"C","answer":"The synthesis of interstellar formaldehyde can be activated by means other than cosmic rays."},{"key":"D","answer":"Simple molecules can be synthesized by means of tunneling."},{"key":"E","answer":"Classical chemical reactionsdo not occur at temperatures close to absolute zero."}],"right":["A"],"parent":1},{"question":"Which of the following best describes the hypothesis of Hoyle and Wickramasinghe as it is presented in the passage?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"Cosmic rays can directly synthesize complex organic molecules."},{"key":"B","answer":"The galactic clouds are the places where prebiological evolution of compounds necessary to life occurred."},{"key":"C","answer":"Interstellar formaldehyde can be synthesized by tunneling."},{"key":"D","answer":"Molecules of interstellar formaldehyde can evolve into complex organic molecules."},{"key":"E","answer":"Complex organic molecules can be synthesized from stable polysaccharides such as cellulose and starch."}],"right":["D"],"parent":1},{"question":"Which of the following best describes the organization of the first two paragraphs of the passage?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"The author cites a basic principle of classical chemistry and then describes the research from which that principle was developed."},{"key":"B","answer":"The author cites an apparent contradiction to the principles of classical chemistry and then explains the process of a chemical reaction to show there is in fact no contradiction."},{"key":"C","answer":"the author describes the role of heat in chemical reactions and then offers a detailed explanation of its function."},{"key":"D","answer":"The author presents a law of classical chemistry in order to introduce a kind of chemical reaction that differs from it and then explains the essential difference between the two."},{"key":"E","answer":"The author presents the fundamental rules of classical chemistry in order to introduce an explanation of a specific chemical reaction. "}],"right":["D"],"parent":1}],"parent":["This is not to deny that the Black gospel music of the\nearly twentieth century differed in important ways from the\nslave spirituals. Whereas spirituals were created and \ndisseminated in folk fashion, gospel music was composed,\n(5) published, copyrighted, and sold by professionals. Nevertheless,\nimprovisation remained central to gospel music.\nOne has only to listen to the recorded repertoire of gospel\nsongs to realize that Black gospel singers rarely sang a\nsong precisely the same way twice and never according to\n(10)its exact musical notation. They performed what jazz musicians\ncall \"head arrangements\" proceeding from their own\nfeelings and from the way \"the spirit\" moved them at the\ntime. This improvisatory element was reflected in the manner in\nwhich gospel music was published. Black gospel\n(15)composers scored the music intended for White singing\ngroups fully, indicating the various vocal parts and the\naccompaniment, but the music produced for Black singers\nincluded only a vocal line and piano accompaniment.","About a century ago, the Swedish physical scientist\nArrhenius proposed a law of classical chemistry that relates\nchemical reaction rate to temperature. According to the\nArrhenius equation, chemical reaction are increasingly\n(5) unlikely to occur as temperatures approach absolute zero,\nand at absolute zero (zero degrees Kelvin, or minus 273\ndegrees Celsius) reactions stop. However, recent experimental \nevidence reveals that although the Arrhenius equation is generally \naccurate indescribing the kind of chemical\n(10)reaction that occurs at relatively high temperatures,\nat temperatures closer to zero a quantum-mechanical effect known\nas tunneling comes into play; this effect accounts for \nchemical reactions that are forbidden by the principles of \nclassical chemistry. Specifically, entire molecules can \"tunnel\"\n(15)through the barriers of repulsive forces from other \nmolecules and chemically react even though these molecules do\nnot have sufficient energy, according to classical chemistry,\nto overcome the repulsive barrier.\n The rate of any chemical reaction, regardless of the tem-\n(20)perature at which it takes place, usually depends on a very\nimportant characteristic known as its activation energy. Any\nmolecule can be imagined to reside at the bottom of a \nsocalled potential well of energy. A chemical reaction corresponds to the transition of a molecule from the bottom of\n(25)one potential well to the bottom of another. In classical\nchemistry, such a transition can be accomplished only by\ngoing over the potential barrier between the wells, the\nheight of which remains constant and is called the \nactivation energy of the reaction. In tunneling, the reacting mole-\n(30)cules tunnel from the bottom of one to the bottom of another\nwell without having to rise over the barrier between the\ntwo wells. Recently researchers have developed the concept\nof tunneling temperature: the temperature below which\n tunneling transitions greatly outnumber Arrhenius transi-\n(35)tions, and classical mechanics gives way to its quantum\ncounterpart.\n This tunneling phenomenon at very low temperatures\nsuggested my hypothesis about a cold prehistory of life:\n the formation of rather complex organic molecules in the\n(40)deep cold of outer space, where temperatures usually reach\nonly a few degrees Kelvin. Cosmic rays (high-energy protons \nand other particles) might trigger the synthesis of\nsimple molecules, such as interstellar formaldehyde, in\n dark clouds of interstellar dust. Afterward complex organic\n(45)molecules would be formed, slowly but surely, by means\nof tunneling. After I offered my hypothesis, Hoyle and\nWickramasinghe argued that molecules of interstellar \nformaldehyde have indeed evolved into stable polysaccharides\nsuch as cellulose and starch. Their conclusions, although\n(50)strongly disputed, have generated excitement among investigators such as myself who are proposing that the galactic\nclouds are the places where the prebiological evolution of\ncompounds necessary to life occurred."]}